<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><title>snobservant</title><link href="http://www.snobservant.com/" rel="alternate"></link><link href="http://www.snobservant.com/feeds/food.atom.xml" rel="self"></link><id>http://www.snobservant.com/</id><updated>2017-03-12T00:00:00-08:00</updated><entry><title>How to Go From Chitterlin' to Michelin</title><link href="http://www.snobservant.com/food/2017/frou-frou-food/" rel="alternate"></link><published>2017-03-12T00:00:00-08:00</published><updated>2017-03-12T00:00:00-08:00</updated><author><name></name></author><id>tag:www.snobservant.com,2017-03-12:food/2017/frou-frou-food/</id><summary type="html">&lt;p&gt;Are the in-laws coming over for dinner?  Got nothing in your kitchen that wouldn't be found in a 24-hour gas station off the Missingbodiesville exit?  No worries.  This reference guide will help you present the truly inedible dishes you nuke up in the microwave as haute cuisine, even as you feed your discerning in-laws a lot lizard diet.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;    &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Bread Basket&lt;/em&gt;    &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Before&lt;/strong&gt;: Airline pretzel packets coughed on by the guy next to you in coach.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;After&lt;/strong&gt;: Bow-tie baby baguettes pointedly punctuated with marine rock salt crystals and dusted with neighbour-harvested rocket-mist reputed to be bestowed with immunity-enhancing properties.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;
&lt;em&gt;Soup du Jour&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Before&lt;/strong&gt;:  An ancient-ass brick of off-brand ramen.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;After&lt;/strong&gt;: Millennium-aged tresses of the caryopsis fruit cultivated from the Levant, braised with waves of gentle Caribbean cotton confit.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;
&lt;em&gt;Antipasto&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Before&lt;/strong&gt;: Slim Jims that were probably in a tweaker's pants before the 7-11 security tackled him and returned them to the inventory.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;After&lt;/strong&gt;: An ecstatically celebrated farmhouse medley exquisitely infused with relentless umami and crafted into a pocket-sized corps de cigarillo.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;
&lt;em&gt;Main Course&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Before&lt;/strong&gt;: Kraft Dinner that your granny had in her pantry since World War II.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;After&lt;/strong&gt;: A frontier favorite passed down the grand chef's maternal lineage comprised of jealously-guarded cavatappi coaxed to mingle in a steam-silkened fondue, harmonizing into the ultimate Somerset al dente affair.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;
&lt;em&gt;Dessert&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Before&lt;/strong&gt;: Packets of pop rocks you scooped up from your bank's candy bowl.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;After&lt;/strong&gt;: Volcanic gem-cut sirop de maïs crafted to be woven by the palate into sparkling rose quartz.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;
&lt;em&gt;Digestif&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Before&lt;/strong&gt;: Four Loko that your son gets from his friend's ex-convict older brother.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;After&lt;/strong&gt;: A crescendo of winter barley-guarana bitters kissed with the essence of the green goddess.&lt;/p&gt;</summary></entry></feed>