<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><title>snobservant</title><link href="http://www.snobservant.com/" rel="alternate"></link><link href="http://www.snobservant.com/feeds/science.atom.xml" rel="self"></link><id>http://www.snobservant.com/</id><updated>2017-02-27T00:00:00-08:00</updated><entry><title>Scientific Studies Show Correlation between Anger and Road Rage</title><link href="http://www.snobservant.com/science/2017/road-rage/" rel="alternate"></link><published>2017-02-27T00:00:00-08:00</published><updated>2017-02-27T00:00:00-08:00</updated><author><name></name></author><id>tag:www.snobservant.com,2017-02-27:science/2017/road-rage/</id><summary type="html">&lt;p&gt;On the behalf of ATP (Adams, Turnberg, and Peters) Researchers, I am pleased to bring about a new finding of our study, funded by Feelrealgood University and the Department of Motor Vehicles, to the scientific community.  Why do Homo Sapiens Sapiens engage in aggressive-aggressive, bestial, and territorial behavior while in their vehicles?  Folks, I have wrangled with this very question myself.  We, at ATP Researchers, have proposed a series of hypotheses in hopes of finding the key to alleviating this unspoken, detrimental, quandary in everyday life.  We have isolated numerous chemical, physical, and biological phenomenons, and assessed the possibilities of them being promoting factors of all the "bird flipping", aggression-to-horn transmissions, and "fuck you!"s that occur with considerable frequency on the streets of New York City, the sample of the American populace we studied.  &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Somewhere along the way, I had an epiphany of immeasurable magnitude, and I utilized my mental potential energy in order to support this discovery.  Every ion has a charge.  Every object encounters gravitational friction along Earth's surface.  While lamenting bitterly about the combustion following my hydrochloric acid (HCl) and ammonia mixture that damaged my surgeon-quality laboratory coat, I ruminated on the possibilities of opposing atomic charges (HCl and Ammonia, as I learned the hard way, have an unfavorable ionic compatibility) and interactions in the car and within the driver's  vocal cords and finger tips.  &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Seventy percent of our bodies is comprised of water.  Our bodies also contain trace amounts of copper, silicon, phosphorous and other minerals.  Many of these elements combine with other elements, some being ions - which can provide a positive or negative charge.  It is abundantly possible that the mobile's interior atmosphere, "car air", possesses an extremely negative charge - is hollering an expletive to another driver not a negative manifestation of vexation?  Because most humans interact positively with strangers vis-à-vis, one can only assume that human bodies naturally have a varying degree of a positive charge.  We examined samples of car air in search of offending ions, such as Cl-, O2-, and HCl-.  To my dismay, $15,000 of laboratory observation concluded that there are no significant differences of the composition between the control group of outdoor air samples, and car air.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We then resumed our research, this time considering the energies and forces at play.  The automobile is a dynamic machine, with ever-changing acceleration and power quantities.  With a nod to the concept of the conservation of energy (energy cannot be created nor destroyed), we hypothesized that the erratic forces of air friction, high automobile densities, and inconsistent velocities transferred to the trachea and the hands, where the energy proceeded to accumulate until it became released through a loud insult to someone's maneuvering ability or through the rapid extension of "the finger" outside of the car window.  We trekked to specialized medical institutions to observe preserved samples of fingers and throats, and saturated them in car air to deduce whether any energy concentrated in these regions had no way to circulate in the body, leaving no choice but to drain through muscular impulses and vocal vibrations.  Our hopes rose upon the discovery of pores on the fingertips, but the veins and capillaries all provide outlets for energy release.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;My ray of hope was starting to dim when a miraculous occurrence nearly led me to disregard the theory of evolution in favor of creationism.  I was driving to the laboratory one morning, with my mind muddled by the argument I had with my wife at home.  She insisted that it was my laziness delaying my "much needed" haircut.  I told her to stop reading so much into simple realities.  I simply don't want my hair cut.  I strongly dislike those who partake in futile analyses of day-to-day matters.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;However, I digress.  I merged onto another lane on the freeway, neglecting to check for arriving cars behind.  Sequentially, I heard a shrill honk and incoherent yells, and I then get a glimpse of The Bird in my rearview mirror.  I decided to create an informative interview of the superficially distressing moment.  I poked my head outside the window and asked the perpetrator the reason for his outburst.  A male subject, appearing to be an age of peak fertility, returned the favor, adding: "Because idiot dipshits like you on the road piss me the fuck off!"  This little nugget of information gave me something to base my next study on.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I proceeded to conduct an impromptu one-sided blind study to reveal whether being "pissed off" by fatuous commuters contributed to aggression.  I allowed my original subject to drive past me, and I began collecting data.  I blatantly cut off precisely 20 different test subjects and recorded their behavioral responses.  After asking the subjects for the reason that I was impolitely berated, I received 18 responses relating to the irritation caused by incompetent drivers.  One harried mother in a Lexus SUV, appearing to be potentially menopausal, sped up past me, giving me only a pitiful head shake to reflect on.  The remaining subject launched a projectile at my car, appearing to be a nearly empty super-sized Slurpee.  My calculations confirm that of all the subjects, 90% suggested that "unsafe"/ "stupid" / "dumbass" drivers prompted the abuse.  Out of the subjects that gave me an answer, the percentage stood strong at 100%.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The ATP researchers have informally extended my study, which still yields approximately the same results, with the exception of five responses resembling, "Hey buddy, here's an idea: yap less, drive more", and "If you're gonna ask questions, ask your local DMV how the hell you managed to get a drivers license."  We plan to decipher these responses eventually, but months of observation and study revealed the evidence of anger as motivation to engage in conflict.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We are excited at the prospect of introducing a possible scientific breakthrough to the public.  Everyday we come closer to understanding the human species.  I am personally examining the possibility of this finding bringing us closer to curing AIDS.  I am now eagerly awaiting my Nobel Prize nomination.&lt;/p&gt;</summary></entry></feed>