<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><title>snobservant</title><link href="http://www.snobservant.com/" rel="alternate"></link><link href="http://www.snobservant.com/feeds/work.atom.xml" rel="self"></link><id>http://www.snobservant.com/</id><updated>2017-03-12T00:00:00-08:00</updated><entry><title>Camp Corporatewakki</title><link href="http://www.snobservant.com/work/2017/camp-corporatewakki/" rel="alternate"></link><published>2017-03-12T00:00:00-08:00</published><updated>2017-03-12T00:00:00-08:00</updated><author><name></name></author><id>tag:www.snobservant.com,2017-03-12:work/2017/camp-corporatewakki/</id><summary type="html">&lt;p&gt;“Well team, how about a power breakfast?”  Scott, the Regional Vice Chief Executive General Specialist brightly announced at 4:30 a.m.  Everybody in their swivel chairs rubbed their eyes and groaned.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“I could go for a pop tart…” Brian, an Assistant Internal Markets Overanalyst yawned.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Everyone, where is your passion and company spirit!  We need to kick off our etched-in plans to touch base to reorient you folks.  So let’s hit the ground running!” Scott exclaimed, clapping his hands together as he circled around the ‘nap chairs’.  “And Brian, pop tarts are old hat.  How about some bagels and coffee?"&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Again?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Our company prides itself on consistency and substance.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“And bagels have substance?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Absolutely.  It’s rich with organic air.  You need air to survive.  And you need to survive in order to capture mindshares in the market.  Cream cheese or peanut butter?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Peanut butter.  And none of that low-fat nonsense.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“We always value our employees’ input,” Scott condescendingly purred, patting Brian on the back.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Uh huh.  There’s only low-fat again, isn’t there?”  Brian bumped into a fluorescent lamp, which wobbled.  “God.  It’s too dark to be up this early.  Jesus.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“It seems to me that we need to exercise your observational skills, as well as resolve certain issues regarding your adherence to PC conduct.  Please do not call out to religious figures in our proximity, for we embrace diversity and outsourcing.  But not to worry, we’ll address that in the restroom meeting.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“What?” Brian sighed under his breath as he tossed on his rumpled suit coat.  Scott meticulously reached out and straightened Brian’s tie, smoothed out the wrinkles on the arms of his coat, and ruffled his hair.  Brian hem-hemmed irritably, trying not to lose it.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Rolled out of the wrong side of the swivel chair this morning, didn’t you?  Not a problem, we’ve got bold Colombian.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“More like old Colombian.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Brian, you need to tune in to the needs of our organization and resource-level your contributions of limited value.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Brian stared in disbelief at Scott for a moment.  “I need to use the toilet.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;To his horror, he saw Scott follow him to the washroom, which he noticed had no door.  &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“What’s going on?  Where’s the door?”  Brian panicked, glancing around.  He turned to Scott and raised a brow. “Scott, do you mind giving me some privacy here?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Open door policy!” Scott chirped. “It’s the sacred cow of Fortune 500 companies everywhere!”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Then how unfortunate that there’s no door to open,” Brian snarled.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Just as Scott was about to make a disapproving remark about Brian’s ‘unhelpful outlook and behaviour’, Brian threw his hands up.  “Fine, Scott.  Whatever.  Watch if you really get off on this kind of thing.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Brian squatted over the toilet, resenting the highly-constipating effects of the strict camp diet of balsamic arugula salad, diet coke, bagels and whole-wheat turkey sandwiches.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“1% inspiration, 99% perspiration, Brian!  1% inspiration, 99% perspiration!”  Scott cheered at the entrance.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;After a few “unproductive” minutes of Brian sitting on the toilet, Scott snapped his fingers.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Well, going forward, the best practice would be to execute the brainchild idea that the Senior Executive Marketing Chief Operations Director spearheaded.  We’ll complete the invigorating, team-building jog first thing in the a.m.!  Then we’ll fuel up with more coffee, as allocated in our budget.  This should get things running,” Scott chuckled, elbowing Brian.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Brian would have scratched Scott’s eyeballs out right then and there, but he knew he’d lecture him about the resulting blood being aesthetically demoralizing.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;He walked back to the coffee room and inserted a biodegradable cup (Scott:  “We’re dynamically GREEN now!”) under the spout, only to hear the nozzle spit instead of pour.  Kim, an Executive Vice President of Micromanaging Logistics, was swilling down coffee from an enormous company mug.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Kim, did you fill that whole mug with the last of the coffee?”  Brian asked in disbelief.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“First mover advantage.” Kim shrugged.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“I had fruitcake ordered in, right over there.”  James, a metrosexual Executive of Senior Redundancy, offered.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“I don’t want your fruitcake, I –“&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“We have a zero-tolerance policy for homophobic remarks, Brian.   Before you refused his advance, you should have brought the meshing offer into the boardroom.  I’m afraid I have no option other than to let you go.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Scott pulled a key out his pocket and unlocked the ergonomic handcuffs around Brian’s wrists and threw him under the bus.&lt;/p&gt;</summary></entry></feed>